Guide to the Thornton Wilder Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Personal Papers, 1912-1975; Series III; 5.84; (16 boxes)
  - PERSONAL APPEARANCES
    - Thornton Wilder-Hugh Walpole debate, [1930] (Box 138, Folder 3153)
    - Thornton Wilder speech on democracy: reports and reply by T. S. Eliot, 1957 (Box 138, Folder 3154)
    - "An Evening with Thornton Wilder", 1962 Apr (Box 138, Folder 3155-3159)
    - Reading by Thornton Wilder: invitation, [1960s?] (Box 138, Folder 3160)
  - TRAVEL DOCUMENTS
    - Baggage claims, n.d. (Box 138, Folder 3161)
    - Contract for sailing on the "Amerigo Vespucci", 1959 Oct 30 (Box 138, Folder 3162)
    - Itineraries, 1929-30 (Box 138, Folder 3163-3165)
    - Itineraries, 1939-69, n.d. (Box 139, Folder 3166-3172)
    - Passports, 1921-71 (Box 139, Folder 3173-3176)
    - Vaccination certificates, 1954-70 (Box 139, Folder 3177)
- Printed Material, 1917-1974; Series IV; 3.34; (9 boxes)
  Series IV, Printed Material, is organized into subseries by type of material.
  - NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS
    - Thornton Wilder
      - Awards and honors, 1928-76, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3178-3183)
      - Brief mentions, 1928-69 (Box 140, Folder 3184-3191)
      - Brief mentions, 1970-76, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3192-3195)
      - Interviews and features, 1928-49 (Box 140, Folder 3196-3203)
      - Interviews and features, 1950-69 (Box 140, Folder 3204-3207)
      - Interviews and features, 1970-76, n.d. (Box 141, Folder 3208-3216)
        See also: Oversize, Box 163, folders 3883-3895; and Oversize
      - Lecture and appearance notices, 1928-50, n.d. (Box 141, Folder 3217-3218)
      - Letter to the editor, 1930 Sep 12 (Box 141, Folder 3219)
      - Obituaries and tributes, 1975-76 (Box 141, Folder 3220-3224)
      - Obituaries and tributes, 1976, n.d. (Box 141, Folder 3225-3232)
      - Portraits, n.d. (Box 141, Folder 3233)
    - Other Persons
      - Albee, Edward, 1963-66, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3234)
      - Aubrey, Bob Austin, Mary, 1934-61, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3235)
      - Bankhead, Tallulah, 1955-68 (Box 142, Folder 3236)
      - Beerbohm, Max, 1952-65, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3237)
      - Beer-Hofmann, Richard, 1965 (Box 142, Folder 3238)
      - Bernstein, Leonard, 1966 Nov 3 (Box 142, Folder 3239)
      - Bousquet, Marie-Louise, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3240)
      - Brooks, Gladys, 1968 Jul (Box 142, Folder 3241)
      - Brown, John Mason, 1969 Jul 29 (Box 142, Folder 3242)
      - Buchwald, Art, 1957-59 (Box 142, Folder 3243)
      - Chavez, Angelico, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3244)
      - Clark, Kenneth, 1970 (Box 142, Folder 3245)
      - Colefax, Sybil, 1950 (Box 142, Folder 3246)
      - Copland, Aaron, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 3247)
      - Cornell, Katherine, 1940, 1966 (Box 142, Folder 3248)
      - Cowley, Malcolm, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 3249)
      - Crawford, Cheryl, 1964 Sep 1
      - De Philippo, Edward, 1961 (Box 142, Folder 3250)
      - Freedman, Harold, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3251)
      - Goldstone, Richard, 1965-75, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3252-3256)
      - Gordon, Ruth and Kanin, Garson, 1967-71, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3257-3260)
      - Guthrie, Tyrone, 1955-67, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3261-3262)
      - Harris, Jed, 1963, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3263)
      - Hartney, Harold E., 1938 Mar 20
      - Hotson, Leslie, 1964, 1970 (Box 142, Folder 3264)
      - Hutchins, Robert M., 1941 Apr 8 (Box 142, Folder 3265)
      - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1965 (Box 142, Folder 3266)
      - Kazan, Elia, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3267)
      - Lewis, Sinclair, 1928, 1961 (Box 142, Folder 3268)
      - Luce, Henry Robinson, 1967 Mar (Box 142, Folder 3269)
      - Lyons, Leonard, 1963 Mar
      - Merrick, David, 1966, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3270)
      - Noguchi, Isamu, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3271)
      - Olivier, Laurence, Sir, 1964 (Box 142, Folder 3272)
      - Phelps, William Lyon, 1931, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3273)
      - Pound, Ezra, 1951 (Box 142, Folder 3274)
      - Preminger, Marion, 1957 Nov 8 (Box 142, Folder 3275)
      - Reinhardt, Max, 1938-73, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3276)
      - Robbins, Jerome, 1963 (Box 142, Folder 3277)
      - Rose, Francis, Sir, 1969, 1971 (Box 142, Folder 3278)
      - Sartre, Jean-Paul, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3279)
      - Soong, T. V., 1971 Apr 27 (Box 142, Folder 3280)
      - Stein, Gertrude, 1959-68, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3281-3283)
      - Talma, Louise, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3284)
      - Toklas, Alice B., 1957-74, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3285)
      - Tunney, Gene, 1928-29 (Box 142, Folder 3286-3287)
      - Wardle, Irving, 1974 (Box 142, Folder 3288)
      - Wescott, Glenway, 1962-67 (Box 142, Folder 3289)
      - Wilson, Edmund, 1966 Dec 11 (Box 142, Folder 3290)
      - Worth, Irene, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3291)
      - Wyeth, Andrew, 1965 (Box 142, Folder 3292)
    - Other Subjects
      - Book reviews, 1929-74, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3293)
        See also: Oversize, Box 163, folders 3906-3907 and Box 165, folders 3999-4000
      - Film and television reviews, 1948-70, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3294)
      - Performance reviews, 1930-75, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3295-3297)
        See also: Oversize, Box 163, folders 3897-3898
      - Humor, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3298)
      - Verse, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3299)
      - Miscellaneous subjects, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3300-3301)
        See also: Oversize, Box 163, folders 3899-3904 and Oversize, Box 163, folders 3908-3909
  - PAMPHLETS
    - Authors' League of America: copyright revision of 1965 (Box 143, Folder 3302)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club, 1948-67, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 3303)
    - "D. H. Lawrence Manuscript Collection", 1964 (Box 143, Folder 3304)
    - "The Fifth Year of C.E.M.A.: 1944" [Council for the Encouragement of Music and the Arts] (Box 143, Folder 3305)
    - "G. W. Pabst", 1963 (Box 143, Folder 3306)
    - "Literary Landmarks of Princeton", 1967 (Box 143, Folder 3307)
    - "The MacDowell Colony, Peterborough, New Hampshire", [1968?] (Box 143, Folder 3308)
      With: Program for a MacDowell Colony benefit
    - Widdener, Margaret: "Summers at the Colony", 1964 (Box 143, Folder 3309)
    - "Working with Kazan," Wesleyan Film Program, 1973 (Box 143, Folder 3310)
    - Zauner, Erich: "Amerikanisches Theater", n.d. (Box 143, Folder 3311)
    - "Zwishcen den Zeiten", 1962 (Box 143, Folder 3312)
  - PERIODICALS
    - The American-German Review, 1957 Oct-Nov (Box 143, Folder 3313)
    - The American Writer, 1952 Dec (Box 143, Folder 3314)
    - Blätter der Thomas Mann Gesellschaft, 1970 (Box 143, Folder 3315)
      Inscribed to Wilder by Alice von Kahler
    - Bulletin of the Comediantes, 1951-71 (Box 143, Folder 3316)
    - Columbia Library Columns, 1970 Feb (Box 143, Folder 3317)
    - The Cresset, 1962 Apr (Box 143, Folder 3318)
    - Dramatists Bulletin, 1962 Feb (Box 143, Folder 3319)
    - Eckart, 1960 Jul (Box 143, Folder 3320)
    - The English-Speaking World, 1941 Nov (Box 143, Folder 3321)
    - Equity, 1960 Sep (Box 143, Folder 3322)
    - The Fortune, 1939 (Box 143, Folder 3323)
    - The Griffith Observer, 1963 Mar (Box 143, Folder 3324)
      Annotated by Isabel Wilder
    - Modern Drama, 1963 Dec (Box 143, Folder 3324a)
    - Opera News, 1969 Sep 6 (Box 143, Folder 3325)
    - Saturday Review World, 1974 Aug 10 (Box 143, Folder 3326)
    - University: A Princeton Quarterly, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 3327)
    - Wisconsin State Journal, 1952 Oct
    - Yale Library Gazette, 1970 Apr (Box 143, Folder 3328)
    - Yankee, 1939 Feb (Box 143, Folder 3329)
    - Zeitschrift für die gesamte Neurologie und Psychiatrie, 1930 (Box 143, Folder 3330)
  - PROGRAMS AND EXHIBITION GUIDES
    - Art exhibitions, 1948-74, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 3331-3336)
    - Concerts and operas, 1941-60 (Box 144, Folder 3337-3340)
    - Concerts and operas, 1961-75, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 3341-3346)
    - Miscellanous events, 1946-68, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 3347-3348)
  - THEATER PROGRAMS
    - Arranged alphabetically by title of production.
    - "A" general, 1956-75, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 3349-3357)
    - "A" general, 1956-75, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 3358-3360)
    - "B" general, 1917-64, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 3361-3368)
    - "Ca-Ch" general, 1969-75 (Box 145, Folder 3369-3374)
    - "Co-Cr" general, 1950-75, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 3375-3381)
    - "D" general, 1918-63, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 3382-3389)
    - "E" general, 1965-68, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 3390-3394)
    - "F" general, 1959-64, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 3395-3399)
    - "G" general, 1956-63, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3400-3404)
    - "G" general, 1956-63, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3405-3411)
    - "H" general, 1915-67, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3412-3419)
    - "I" general, 1955-66 (Box 146, Folder 3420-3422)
    - "J" general, 1956-66, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3423-3426)
    - "K" general, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3427-3428)
    - "L" general, 1958, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3429-3432)
    - "M" general, 1955-64, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3433-3439)
    - "M" general, 1955-64, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3440-3450)
    - "N" general, 1961, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3451-3453)
    - "O" general, 1950-69, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3454-3461)
    - "P" general, 1911-65 (Box 147, Folder 3462-3469)
    - "Q" general, 1918, 1959 (Box 147, Folder 3470-3471)
    - "R" general, 1948-66 (Box 147, Folder 3472-3477)
    - "S" general, 1925-67, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 3478-3484)
    - "S" general, 1925-67, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 3485-3494)
    - "T" general, 1916-65, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 3495-3498)
    - "T" general, 1916-65, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 3499-3506)
    - "U-V" general, 1961-64, n.d. (Box 148, Folder 3507-3510)
    - "W" general, 1914-67, n.d. (Box 148, Folder 3511-3517)
    - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 148, Folder 3518-3520)
- Photographs, 1900-1972; Series V; 2.71; (7 boxes)
  Series V, Photographs, is organized into subseries by subject of photograph. Photographs within each subseries are arranged either chronologically or alphabetically.
  - THORNTON WILDER
    - Baby pictures from early albums, 1900-01, n.d. (Box 149, Folder 3521-3525)
      Some pictures include other Wilder children
    - Wilder and family members, 1905-06 (Box 149, Folder 3526-3527)
    - Wilder and family members, "Parker Street, Berkeley", 1907-08 (Box 149, Folder 3528-3529)
    - Studio portrait, "Berkeley, California- 10 years old", 1907 (Box 149, Folder 3530)
    - Postcard shots of Wilder and family members, 1908 (Box 149, Folder 3531)
    - "Mother Wilder and Thornie" (and other children), 1910 (Box 149, Folder 3532)
    - Wilder and other students in school pictures, Chefoo, China, 1912 (Box 149, Folder 3533)
    - "Thacher School--Importance of Being Ernest" (Wilder and cast), [1913?] (Box 149, Folder 3534)
    - Wilder seated, 1915 (Box 149, Folder 3535)
    - Wilder and family, 1915 (Box 149, Folder 3536)
    - "Wilder at Work --Mt. Hermon": postcards, [1915-16?] (Box 149, Folder 3537)
    - Studio portrait, "Oberlin--freshman year", [1915-16] (Box 149, Folder 3538)
    - Portrait of Wilder with glasses, Wilder and Isabel Wilder, and group shot from Oberlin, 1917 (Box 149, Folder 3539)
    - "Corporal Thornton Wilder, 1918" (Box 149, Folder 3540)
      With: printed reproduction of same portrait, 1928
    - Wilder and Janet Wilder, [ca. 1920?] (Box 149, Folder 3541)
    - Wilder and Amos Wilder, 1920 (Box 149, Folder 3542)
    - Wilder and friends at Yale, [ca. 1920?] (Box 149, Folder 3543)
    - "Yale graduation picture, 1920" (Box 149, Folder 3544)
      See also: Oversize, Box 164, folder 3918
    - Wilder posed in classroom, "Lawrenceville, 1922-25" (Box 149, Folder 3545)
    - Studio portrait by Harris and Ewing, Washington, D.C., [1922]
    - Class photo with TNW as teacher, n.d. (Box 149, Folder 3546)
    - Studio portrait by Danford Barney, [1920s] (Box 149, Folder 3547)
      See also: Oversize: Box 164, folder 3921
    - Studio portraits of Wilder in glasses: "Credit this photo to Danford Barney," "about 1924-5-6", [ca. 1925?] (Box 149, Folder 3548)
    - Wilder and family members posed in front of 75 Mansfield Street, [ca. 1925] (Box 149, Folder 3549)
    - Wilder on beach, 1925 (Box 149, Folder 3550)
    - Studio portrait of Wilder marked "'Bridge' picture-- 1927??" (Box 149, Folder 3551)
    - Wilder and family members, marked "Surrey 1928" (Box 149, Folder 3552)
    - Wilder at Axland House, 1928 Jul (Box 149, Folder 3553)
    - Wilder and unidentified friend at Mer de Glace, 1928 Oct (Box 149, Folder 3554)
    - Portrait of Wilder attributed to Doris Ulmann by Isabel Wilder, [1929] (Box 149, Folder 3555)
      See also: Oversize, Box 164, folders 3922-3923
    - Miscellaneous 1920s pictures, n.d. (Box 149, Folder 3556)
    - Proofs and studio portrait of Wilder, [ca. 1930?] (Box 149, Folder 3557-3558)
    - Wilder and unidentified man, "La Venta Inn, Palos Verdes, California", 1930 Jan 8 (Box 149, Folder 3559)
    - Wilder portrait by Lawrence Beall Smith, 1930
    - "U. of Chicago, 1931" (Box 149, Folder 3560)
    - Studio portrait by Ben D. Gross, Tucson, "early 1930s", [ca. 1932?] (Box 149, Folder 3561)
    - Wilder portrait for The Chicagoan, 1932 Feb
    - Portrait, "Chicago--early '30s", [1931-34?] (Box 149, Folder 3562)
    - Studio portrait by Ben Pinchot Studio, New York, 1933
    - Portrait with Isabel Wilder, 1933 Dec (Box 149, Folder 3563)
    - Studio portrait by Blackstone Studios, n.d. (Box 149, Folder 3564)
    - Half-tone portrait by Pirie MacDonald, n.d. (Box 149, Folder 3565)
    - Wilder in Salzburg, 1935-36 (Box 149, Folder 3566)
    - Proof portrait of Wilder standing by Associated News Photo Service, [1938]
    - Wilder and Reinhardt in "The Merchant of Yonkers", 1938 (Box 149, Folder 3567)
    - Wilder with cast members of Our Town, 1939 (Box 150, Folder 3568-3569)
    - Wilder at Peterborough town presentation, [1939?] (Box 150, Folder 3570)
    - Wilder on trip to France, 1939 (Box 150, Folder 3571)
    - Wilder and Paul Osborn, Culver City, CA (Box 150, Folder 3572)
    - Wilder at Yale: Sterling Library, [1930s] (Box 150, Folder 3573)
    - Harem Scenes #1 and 2 (Box 150, Folder 3574)
    - Passport photos, [1930s?] (Box 150, Folder 3575)
    - Wilder in the 1930s (Box 150, Folder 3576)
    - Wilder and unidentified friends, 1940 (Box 150, Folder 3577)
    - "Florida"--Wilder standing in front of automobile (Box 150, Folder 3578)
    - Wilder on South American trip, 1941 (Box 150, Folder 3579)
    - "Abel Romero Castillo and a journalist" with Wilder, Foto Jordan, Guayaquil, Ecuador, 1941 (Box 150, Folder 3580)
    - Wilder and group at the Cafe Rosado, Guayaquil, signed by the attendees, including Abel Romero Castillo, 1941 May 6 (Box 150, Folder 3581)
    - Portraits of Wilder in landscape [Mexico?] "printed from Goski's negatives", 1942 (Box 150, Folder 3582)
    - "Major Thornton N. Wilder 1943" proofs of studio portrait by Petrelle Studio, New, Haven (Box 150, Folder 3583)
    - Studio portrait of Wilder in Army uniform, Petrelle Studio, New Haven, 1943
    - Portrait of Wilder in Army uniform, [1943?] (Box 150, Folder 3584)
    - Wilder and group portrait in uniform (Box 150, Folder 3585)
    - Wilder in uniform "T.N.W.- Rec'd July 12, 1944" (Box 150, Folder 3586)
    - Wilder in uniform, Florida, 1945 (Box 150, Folder 3587)
    - Photograph of Wilder in uniform with Arden Paul, Doc Gregory, and Stephanie (signed by them) at the Clover Club, Miami, Florida, 1945 (Box 150, Folder 3588)
    - Snapshots of Wilder and military colleagues, 1945 (Box 150, Folder 3589)
    - Wilder and members of unidentified military wedding party in Great Britain, [1945?] (Box 150, Folder 3590)
    - Wilder, Janet Wilder, and Toby Dakin "The Troika....Washington, D.C.", [1945?] (Box 150, Folder 3591)
    - Portraits of Wilder seated in study: "Credit Fred Hess and Son, Atlantic City, N.J.", [1946 Feb] (Box 150, Folder 3592)
    - Wilder and friend in Florida, 1947 May (Box 150, Folder 3593)
    - Portrait of seated Wilder by V. R. Deane, Jacksonville Beach, Florida, [1947?] (Box 150, Folder 3594)
    - Wilder, Isabel Wilder, and "the Schiffelers", 1947 Jun 23 (Box 150, Folder 3595)
    - Wilder, Isabel Wilder, Rosalie Stuart and, June T. (Box 150, Folder 3596)
    - Wilder, Isabel Wilder, Lilian Gish and Michael Redgrave, 1947 (Box 150, Folder 3597)
    - Portrait of Wilder by Irving Penn, Vogue Studios, New York, [1947 Aug]
    - Wilder standing in front of automobile, [1947?] (Box 150, Folder 3598)
    - Studio portrait of Wilder in profile by Petrelle Studios, New Haven, [1947] (Box 150, Folder 3599)
      See also: Oversize, Box 164, folders 3933-3934
    - Studio portrait of Wilder facing front by Petrelle Studios, New Haven, [1947] (Box 150, Folder 3600)
      See also: Oversize, Box 164, folder 3935
    - Wilder as Mr. Antrobus, photograph by Carl Van Vechten, 1948 Aug 5 (Box 150, Folder 3601)
    - Wilder as Mr. Antrobus with cast members, photograph by Carl Van Vechten, 1948 Aug 18 (Box 150, Folder 3602)
    - Wilder and unidentified friends, [1948?] (Box 150, Folder 3603)
    - Portraits of Wilder in striped tie, by Russell Kuhner, [1948-49?] (Box 150, Folder 3604)
    - Wilder and Isabel Wilder, Milano, 1949 Jan (Box 150, Folder 3605)
    - Photo session of April 17, 1949: portraits of Wilder with cigarette, Wilder with Isabel Wilder, Wilder with friends at Deepwood Drive, 1949 Apr 17 (Box 150, Folder 3606-3607)
    - Life portraits and group portrait of participants in Goethe Festival, including Albert Schweitzer, Aspen, 1949 Aug (Box 150, Folder 3608)
    - Portrait of Wilder by Fred Stein, New York City, 1949
    - Miscellaneous 1940s, n.d. (Box 150, Folder 3609)
    - Wilder and other participants at conference, Rapallo, Italy, 1950 Apr (Box 150, Folder 3610)
    - Wilder as Stage Manager in production of Our Town, Wellesley, 1950 Aug (Box 150, Folder 3611)
    - Portrait of Wilder with bust of Pan, [1950?] (Box 150, Folder 3612)
    - Wilder and other honorary degree recipients, Northeastern University, 1951 Jun 24 (Box 150, Folder 3613)
    - Wilder and other honorary degree recipients, Oberlin College, 1952 (Box 150, Folder 3614)
    - Wilder at MacDowell Colony with Marian MacDowell, Paul Nordoff, Nikolai Lopatnikoff, and Margaret Widdener, 1952 (Box 150, Folder 3615)
    - Wilder with Helen Morley Woodruff at rehearsal of George Spelvin Players, [1952?] (Box 150, Folder 3616)
    - Wilder with wife of "Kiddie, friend [of] G.S." in Geneva, [ca. 1952?] (Box 150, Folder 3617)
    - Wilder and Isabel Wilder seated outdoors, 1953 Jun (Box 150, Folder 3618)
    - Wilder at shore: "Blue Hill, Maine, July 31, 1953", 1953 Jul 31 (Box 150, Folder 3619)
    - Wilder and friends, "Compliments of Albert Peterson", [1953?] (Box 151, Folder 3620)
    - Wilder in lecture hall, [1953?] (Box 151, Folder 3621)
      With: one shot of Wilder in landscape with building
    - Portrait of Wilder on telephone, "Newcastle....Record...A Kelmsley Photograph", 1954 Aug (Box 151, Folder 3622)
    - Portrait of Wilder by Atelier Zemann, Heidelberg, "Autumn '54", 1954 (Box 151, Folder 3623)
    - Wilder visit to Berlin, 1954 Sep (Box 151, Folder 3624)
      Includes Wilder with cast of production of The Matchmaker; Wilder with U. S. High Commissioner James B. Conant
    - Strip snapshots of Wilder, [1954] (Box 151, Folder 3625)
    - Wilder and friends in Villars, [ca. 1954] (Box 151, Folder 3626)
    - Wilder standing in landscape, by Galleria Cristallo, "Feb 55", 1955 Feb (Box 151, Folder 3627)
    - Wilder, Isabel Wilder, and Italian friend in Rapallo, 1955 Feb (Box 151, Folder 3628)
    - Wilder with Terry Catherman and Isabel Wilder in snow, [1955?] (Box 151, Folder 3629)
    - Wilder with Marion Preminger, [ca. 1955?] (Box 151, Folder 3630)
    - Passport photos of Wilder by Rogers Studio, New Haven "June 1956", 1956 Jun (Box 151, Folder 3631)
    - Portrait of Wilder taken at Saratoga Springs, "Life Photo by Alfred Eisenstadt", 1956 Jul 8
    - Portrait of Wilder by G. D. Hackett, 1957 (Box 151, Folder 3632-3634)
      See also: Oversize, Box 164, folder 3939
    - Portrait of Wilder in Frankfurt by Foto-Rücker, 1957 Dec (Box 151, Folder 3635)
    - Wilder, Isabel Wilder and friends at theater, [1957?] (Box 151, Folder 3636)
    - Wilder and friends, including Waldo Greene, 1958 (Box 151, Folder 3637)
    - Portrait of Wilder in armchair, "Sizer", 1958 Oct 16 (Box 151, Folder 3638)
    - Wilder and friends on European trip, 1959 (Box 151, Folder 3639-3640)
    - Portrait of Wilder, "Midnight sailing The Bremen, Service, 1959 Oct 15 (Box 151, Folder 3641)
    - Portrait of Wilder outdoors, [1959?] (Box 151, Folder 3642)
    - Wilder and staff members of Radio Free Europe's Munich offices, [1950s] (Box 151, Folder 3643-3644)
    - Wilder, Sylvia Beach and two friends, [1950s] (Box 151, Folder 3644a)
    - Wilder seated in theater, "Deepwood 1960?" (Box 151, Folder 3645)
    - Wilder with cover of reissue of The Bridge of San Luis Rey, 1960
    - Various 1960 pictures, n.d. (Box 151, Folder 3646)
    - Wilder and Heyek family at Hotel Taft, [ca. 1961] (Box 151, Folder 3647)
    - Various 1962 pictures, n.d. (Box 151, Folder 3648-3650)
    - Wilder standing before building, "At Tucson, Spring 1963" (Box 152, Folder 3651)
    - Wilder "At the Troxells", 1963 Aug 21 (Box 152, Folder 3652)
    - Wilder being presented with the Medal of Freedom, 1963 Dec
    - Various 1963 pictures, n.d. (Box 152, Folder 3653)
    - Portrait of Wilder by Bernice B. Perry, "summer 1964" (Box 152, Folder 3654)
    - Wilder with Carol Channing, inscribed, 1964
    - Various 1964 pictures, n.d. (Box 152, Folder 3655)
    - Wilder at the White House with Lyndon Johnson (Natonal Medal Award), 1965 May 4 (Box 152, Folder 3656-3657)
    - Portraits of Wilder by Pix, Incorporated, [ca. 1965?] (Box 152, Folder 3658)
    - Various 1966 pictures, n.d. (Box 152, Folder 3659)
    - Wilder at Deepwood Drive, [ca. 1968?] (Box 152, Folder 3660)
    - Wilder portrait for the New Haven Register, 1969 Jan 5
    - Various 1969 pictures (Box 152, Folder 3661)
    - 1969 pictures with others (Box 152, Folder 3662)
    - Portrait studies of Wilder by Jill Krementz, 1973 (Box 152, Folder 3663)
    - Portrait of Wilder seated in study at Deepwood Drive, 1970 Mar (Box 152, Folder 3664)
    - Various 1970 pictures (Box 152, Folder 3665)
    - Wilder and friends at Deepwood Drive, [ca. 1972?] (Box 152, Folder 3666)
    - Wilder at Deepwood Drive, [ca. 1973] (Box 152, Folder 3667)
    - Wilder portraits, n.d. (Box 152, Folder 3668-3670)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS OF OTHERS
    - Beerbohm, Max, 1950, 1952 (Box 153, Folder 3671)
      With: notes to Thornton and Isabel Wilder
    - Browne, E. Martin, 1971 Oct (Box 153, Folder 3672)
    - Catherman, T. F., 1955 Mar (Box 153, Folder 3673)
    - Channing, Carol (includes London opening of Hello, Dolly ), [1960s] (Box 153, Folder 3674)
    - Channing, Carol and Isabel Wilder, inscribed to Wilder (Box 153, Folder 3675)
    - Chou, J. T. and family, 1971-72 (Box 153, Folder 3676)
    - Cohen, Harriet, inscribed to Wilder, n.d. (Box 153, Folder 3677)
    - Colefax, Sybil, n.d. (Box 153, Folder 3678)
      With: photos of Stanway House, including one of H. G. Wells
    - Cornell, Katherine, inscribed to Thornton Wilder, 1917 (Box 153, Folder 3679)
    - Dakin, Toby, 1943 (Box 153, Folder 3680)
    - De Bardeleben family, 1973 (Box 153, Folder 3681)
    - De Bosis, Lauro, n.d. (Box 153, Folder 3682)
    - Eliot, Charles William and celebrants of his 90th birthday, [1924] (Box 153, Folder 3683)
      Group portrait includes "Gov. Channing H. Cox, Chief Justice W. H. Taft, C. T. Grave of Associated Harvard Clubs... Justice E. T. Sanford, Pres. A. Lawrence Lowell of Harvard; Pres. James Howland Angell of Yale, Dean L. B. R. Briggs." Photograph credited to the Keystone View Company.
    - Farrow, Mia and family (Box 153, Folder 3684)
      Some photographs inscribed to Wilder